Red...
Just like the colour of her hair.
Red.
Her hair is redder than blonde red hair,
the same color as my hands.
Long red hair... yes, that's it.
Give me your life.
Episode 1 - I, Got a Girlfriend!
I want to squeeze your boobs.
I agree with you Hyoudou Issei-kun!
Stop it. You're making me upset.
Matsuda, Motohama,
why do we enroll in this school?
The private school, Kuou Academy, changes from an all-girls school to a co-ed school.
So, there are more girls than guys here,
and also many beautiful girls from abroad!
That's what makes us guys valuable.
In other words, we will become popular without having to try.
You can't mess it up!
In short, we'll have a harem!
Yes, a successful life filled with boobs awaits us!
Spirit! Spirit!
...is what we expect
It's spring now, our sophomore year, and we still don't have girlfriends.
Stop it. You're making me upset.
We must not give up!
We still have a chance!
Kiba!
What will you do next?
Hey, wanna go karaoke with us?
Sorry, but I have club activities right now.
What a shame, huh!
Thank you for inviting me. I apologize.
Kiba Yuuto, class 2-C.
He's the idol of all the girls in school...
...and an enemy to us boys!
Damn it!
He is liked by girls simply because he is handsome, quite smart, and kind!
Stop it. You're making me upset.
This world is really unfair, huh?
Oh, it's almost time!
Where are you going?
Murayama's boobs are really big, you know!
The size is 82-70-81.
Katase's legs are smooth!
The size is 78.5-65-79.
During gym class I accidentally found this place!
Hey!
Let me take a peek too!
Don't enjoy it alone!
Damn you!
Is there anyone outside!
You...!
What is it?
Hey, Matsuda, Motoha...ma...
You again?
Seriously.
W-Wait.
Hyoudou pervert!
They really hit me with their bamboo swords.
You're so unlucky, Issei.
You guys left me!
I wouldn't complain if I at least saw some boobs,
but I didn't see it and they-
So, there really are people in this old building, huh?
Red hair is so beautiful, isn't it?
Rias Gremory.
The size is 99-58-90...
...and she was a member of the Occult Research Club for 3 years.
She said her family came from Northern Europe.
The guy from earlier...
Excuse me?
I mean the guy in the middle.
He's in class 2-B.
If I'm not mistaken, his name is Hyoudou.
What's up with him?
Nothing. Maybe I just saw it wrong.
It's not a difficult problem.
Even though I've increased the difficulty a bit.
So?
I hope the next one is harder.
My school life was gloomy.
Would my time at school be wasted without the chance to touch boobs?
A-Anu...
You are Hyoudou Issei-kun from Kuou Academy,
right?
Yes?
I've never seen that uniform before.
I wonder which school she is from.
She is beautiful!
Well...
W-What do you need with me?
Hyoudou-kun, are you dating someone?
N-No.
I'm grateful!
Huh?
W-Well, do you want to go out with me?
What did you just say?
I always see you passing by here and...
I know you are...
H-Hey, is this...?
I ask...
Please be my boyfriend!
A-Are you serious?!
Wake up, wake up!
I-If you don't wake up, I-I'll kiss you, you know!
Wake up-
Wh-What?!
Why?!
This is Amano Yuuma-chan.
They are my friends, Matsuda and Motohama.
Nice to meet you guys.
And she...
...my girlfriend.
You guys hurry up and find a girlfriend too!
Come on, Yuuma-chan.
Okay!
Y-You traitor!
Date?
Yes, this Sunday. Can't?
N-No, of course I can!
I'm grateful!
See you!
Okay! See you.
I can't wait for our date!
Yes, so do I.
Date, date!
Sounds great!
Excellent!
So.
It turns out that your interest is true...
Exactly right.
Choosing you to watch over him was the right choice.
Chairman, what should I do?
I will make some preparations,
But, it all depends on him.
She is a little late.
Please take a look!
I didn't mean to take one.
"We grant your request"?
It's like a trick.
Issei!
Good morning, Yuuma-chan!
Sorry, have you been waiting long?
No, I just came.
I've always wanted to say that!
What is it?
Are you okay?
Today is such a fun day, huh!
Yes, what a great day!
T-This is my big chance.
I did it!
Hey, Issei.
Would you do something for me to commemorate our first date?
Co-Could she be asking...
W-What do you want?
Can you die?
What?
That...
Eh?
Sorry, Yuuma-chan. Can you say it again?
It seems like my ears heard wrong.
Can you die?
I saw it!
I see it clearly!
Even though it was short, I saw real boobs!
Finally I saw real boobs for the first time!
And she's a beautiful girl too!
Is this what you call a show?
Not that.
Now is not the time for that.
Wing?
Even if it's for a while, playing puppy love with you is fun too.
I will keep this gift from you.
So...
Yuuma-chan?
...please die.
Sorry, your life is a threat to us.
So we have to kill you as soon as possible.
Blame God for implanting the Sacred Gear in your body.
W... what?
Thank you for the pleasant memories.
Seriously.
I'm going to die in this small park because of the strange thing that just happened?
If you want to kill me, at least let me squeeze your boobs.
Even though I can only see a glimpse, your boobs are really big, Yuuma-chan.
Red.
Red, like her hair.
Her hair is redder than blonde red hair,
the same color as my hands.
What did I say?
I almost died.
It's over. Damn it.
I can't move my body.
Damn. I don't even know why I have to die.
But, my life is so bad.
If I could live again, I... I...
Rias-senpai... Her beautiful red hair...
If I die, I want to die on the chest of a beautiful girl like her.
You called me, right?
Who-Who?
If you die, I will take you.
Wings again.
You will...
...give up your life for me.
Wake up or I'll kill you.
Wake up. If you don't, I'll kill you.
Wa-
It's very heavy.
This thing gives me weird dreams.
Dream?
You really don't remember Yuuma-chan?
I told you I don't know her.
You never introduced a girl like that to us, and there's no way you have a girlfriend!
There's no way you're bald!
I have the email address-
There isn't any!
Yuuma-chan's phone number and email...
...is lost.
Rias-senpai!
Correct?
She is beautiful as usual.
She is so beautiful!
Yes, it's the scent, that makes it so amazing!
You must be going a little crazy because of your perverted fantasies.
I'm not like you guys! I'm sure-
That's enough. Today we gather at my house.
We will enjoy my special collection together!
DVD Por-
They are disgusting.
All they think about is perverted things.
Disgusting.
Pervert.
I mean, I have some of the latest "adult tape" releases.
Oh, that's amazing!
Issei, it's time you replaced your fantasies with real erotica.
Changed!
This is Momo-chan's new work, Kaben Rider Pinky!
Quite difficult to get.
It turns out that there really is something strange.
Is it possible that the precious memories of the past few days were just a dream?
If that's true, what happened to my original memories from those days?
Hey!
What's wrong, Issei?
You're a fan of Momozono Momo, right?
Yes.
Oh yeah, let's turn off the lights to make it even more exciting.
(Deadly Lick!)
So exciting!
Is not it?
Raider's riding moves are amazing!
Hey, it's not dead.
Huh? What did you say?
The lights don't go out.
What?
What are you talking about?
Not that.
The lights are off
I don't feel the light.
But can see it.
I saw it.
Excuse me.
I'm going home first.
Hey, are you not feeling well?
I can see it clearer than during the day.
And, for some reason, I felt a power flowing through my body.
No, buy me one!
If you keep whining, I'll leave!
No!
Why can I hear voices so far away?!
What happened to me?
My body is feeling weird.
This park...
Oh yeah, right here.
Here I am on a date with Yuuma-chan.
Yuuma-chan...
I don't want to believe it.
What?
What a shame.
Why is this? I can't stop shaking.
(Maybe this is my lucky day to meet you in this place.)
I just meant to step back a bit!
Want to run away, huh?
I don't know what's happening!
Hair?
Yuuma-chan?
This was why low level creatures were so troublesome.
A-Am I dreaming again?
I can't feel the presence of my master or my friends.
You didn't try to escape or create a magic circle.
Analyzing the situation, you must be lost.
Then I can kill.
If this is the same dream,
I'd rather have a pretty girl do it than a guy like him!
Sick.
It really hurts.
It doesn't hurt this much when Yuuma-chan does it...
It hurts, right?
That light is a painful poison for a race like yours.
I thought it would kill you instantly, but you're quite tough.
Don't worry. I'll finish you off soon.
It's useless now.
Someone... help me!
Did you do that?
I don't think so.
Don't touch the child.
Red hair...
Ri-Rias-senpai...
Who are you?
Damn you!
Red hair... I see.
You must be from the Gremory family.
I'm Rias Gremory. How are you, Outcast Angel?
Oh, wow.
Who would have thought that this area was under the control of the Gremory family?
Is he a member of your family?
I won't forgive you if you hurt him.
Well, I apologize for today,
but you better not let your slaves wander around on their own.
Someone like me would probably kill him while he was out walking, you know?
Thank you for the advice.
So let me remind you too...
...I won't let you do something like this again.
You too, heir to the Gremory family.
My name is Donnasiege.
I hope we never meet again.
I was reckless. Who would have thought he would meet the Forsaken Angel.
If this continues he could die.
I won't let him die.
Because, he is mine...
Wake up, sir!
Sir-
It's very heavy.
I had a strange dream again.
Why does this happen at night after-
Huh? Why am I naked?
Where are my panties?
Rias-senpai!?
Is it morning already?
B-Boobs!
Good morning.
A-Anu, Rias-senpai, w-why are you...?
Wait, this is just a dream?
Yes, I'm still dreaming!
Everything you experience is real.
I'm Rias Gremory...
I am a devil...
T-The Devil?
And also your master.
Nice to have you, Kyoudou Issei-kun.
Imagine something very powerful.
I will be the Harem King!
Give me strength!
Well, I got a stupid little brother.